Guide to the Doris Duke American Indian oral history project audio recordings 1949-1972
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Charlie Sam, 1971 June 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1119-II)
- Mary Yazzie (Navajo), 1971 June 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1120-I)
  Wide Ruins
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow and Clifford Big Thumb.
- Mary Yazzie (Navajo), 1971 June 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1120-II)
- Martin Link, 1971 July 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1121)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester and B. Lee.
- Mr. and Mrs. O.C. Haven, 1971 July 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1122)
  Interviewed and recorded by G. C. Crampton, V. Anderson, and J. D. Sylvester.
- J. Lee Correll, 1971 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1123)
- Archie Chischilly (Navajo), 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1124)
  Chief Ranger of the Navajo Nation
- Mary Tom, 1971 June 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1125-I)
  Vegetable Dyes
  Reel-Reel A-Tape, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 16 minutes.
  Interviewed, recorded, and translated by B. Lee.
- Mary Tom, 1971 June 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1125-II)
  Reel-Reel A-Tape, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 42 minutes.
- Lady Singer-Naschiti (Navajo), 1971 June 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1126-I)
  Native Songs
  Recorded by E. Bulow, Translated by B. Lee.
- Lady Singer-Naschiti (Navajo), 1971 June 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1126-II)
- Ernest Franklin (Navajo), 1971 July 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1127-I&II)
  Coyote Canyon
  Translation of interview tracks 1-7, followed by original interview tracks 8-13.
  Interviewed and recorded by N. Bulow.
- Ernest Franklin (Navajo), 1971 July 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1128-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 5 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by N. Bulow, Translated by B. Lee.
- Kate Lynch (Navajo), 1971 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1129-I)
  Antelope Lake
  Interviewed and recorded b7y E. Bulow and C. Big Thumb. translated by B. Lee.
- Kate Lynch (Navajo), 1971 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1129-II)
- John Lynch (Navajo), 1971 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1130-I)
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow, translated by B. Lee.
- John Lynch (Navajo), 1971 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1130-II&III)
  Original interview in Navajo.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 3 minutes.
- William Kien, 1971 July 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1131-I&II)
  Interview 2
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 3 hours 1 minute.
  Interviewed and recorded by M. Decarlo.
- Lee Benally (Navajo), 1971 June 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1132-I)
  Continuation of interview in native language.
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 32 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow in Red Rock, Arizona.
  Note that the manuscript for this item is only available as a rough draft in an unbound file.
- Lee Benally (Navajo), 1971 June 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1132-II)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 1 minute.
- Lee Benally (Navajo), 1971 June 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1132-III)
- Jess McNevins, 1971 June 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1133)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 22 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by S. Galassi.
- Mary Jamison, Rose Fish, 1971 June 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1134)
  Interviewed and recorded by S. Galassi
- Joe Tevenyouma (Hopi), 1965 June; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1135)
  "Conversations at Hopi Show"
  Interviewed and recorded by B. Wright for the Museum of Northern Arizona Library Collection.
- Jimmie Kewanwytewa (Hopi), 1964; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1136-I&II)
  Government Employment
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 15 minutes.
- Grant L. Tapija, 1967 December 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1137)
  Oral History
  Speed gets alittle fast as the tape goes on.
  Interviewed and recorded by B. Carr
- Laura Runke, 1967 August 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1138)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Levy and J. Beasler
- Laura Runke, 1967 August 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1139)
- Laura Runke, 1967 August 31; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1140)
- Pearl Anderson (Cherokee), 1971 September 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1141)
  Interviewed and recorded by Helen M. Amgwerd in Anaheim, California
- Navajo Ethnology, 1971 July; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1142)
  Navajo Ethnology
  (From Miss Bartlett's Collection housed in the Museum of Northern Arizona's Library)
  Interviewed and recorded by J.D Sylvester and B. Lee
- Navajo Code Talkers, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1143)
  Navajo Code Talkers reunion.
- Navajo Code Talkers Reunion (Morning Session), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1144)
  Navajo Code Talkers Reunion.
  Interviewed and recorded by N. Bulow
- Navajo Code Talkers Reunion (morning session), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1145)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 2 hours 4 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by B. Frank
- Navajo Code Talkers Reunion (Morning Session), 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1146-I-IV)
  Tape I- Partial translation of tape from parts of the banquet at the reunion.
  4 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (6 CDs) Total running time 4 hours 1 minute.
  Recorded by N. Bulow, J. D. Sylvester, and B. Frank.
- Navajo Code Talkers Reunion (Afternoon Session), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1147-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 36 minutes.
- Alan Charley (Navajo), 1971 July 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1148)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 17 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester and B. Lee
- Shorty Begay, Sam Begay (Navajo), 1971 July 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1149-I)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 34 minutes.
- Shorty Begay, Sam Begay (Navajo), 1971 July 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1149-II)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 51 minutes.
- Jeff Young (Navajo), 1971 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1150-I)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 28 minutes.
- Jeff Young (Navajo), 1971 July 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1150-II)
  Reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 1 minute.
- Song / Dance Practice, 1966 January; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1151)
  Song and Dance Practice; Dances, procedures ect.
  Interviewed and recorded by C. Ferguson and B. Wright.
- Gordon Peywa (Zuni), 1970 July 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1152)
  Interviewed and recorded by Dr. C. G Crampton, M. J Anderson, V. Anderson, and J. D. Sylvester.
- John Bennett (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1153-I)
  Creation of sweathouse, sheep, herding songs. Songs by John Singer.
  Translation of the original tape.
  Interviewed and recorded by B. Lee
- John Bennett (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1153-II)
  Original interview/songs in native language.
  Interviewee not identified at the beginning of tape.
- John Bennett (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1154-I)
  Animal Sunrise song, changing woman's song
- John Bennett (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1154-II)
- John Bennett (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1155)
  Eagle Song Story, Lightning and Thunder
- John Benally; Judge Dean Wilson, 1970 July; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1156)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 54 minutes.
- George B. Soce (Navajo), 1971 July 11; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1157)
  Navajo Tribal Water Development
  Code Talking, marines.
  Interviewed and recorded by C. G. Crampton and V. Anderson
- Reverend R.O. Hawthorne, 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1158)
- Dan Akee (Navajo), 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1159)
  Code Talker experiences with Sam Holiday
- Raphael Yazzie (Navajo), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1160)
  Fourth Division-Code Talker experiences
- Wilfred Billy (Navajo), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1161)
  Guidance counseling at Shiprock High School
- James Nahkai Jr. (Navajo), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1162)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester
- Teddy Draper, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1163-I,II,III)
  3 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 28 minutes.
- Harold Foster, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1164)
- Frank Thompson (Navajo), 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1165)
  Code Talker, head of Tribal Maintenance.
- Thomas H. Begay (Navajo), 1971 July 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1166)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester, translated by B. Lee
- Samuel T. Holiday, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1167-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotape, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 54 minutes.
- Sidney Bedoni, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1168-I&II)
  Tape I follows II.
- Samuel J. Smith (Navajo), 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1169)
- Dennie Hosteen, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1170)
- William McCabe (Navajo), 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1171)
- Thomas Claw (Navajo), 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1172)
- John Anthony Reyna, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1173)
- Charles Reid, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1174)
  Reel-to-reel audiotape,compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 28 minutes.
- Angelina Medina, 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1175)
  Tuition Controversy
- Eric La Rose, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1176)
- Buford Wayt, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1177)
- Francis Duckey (Paiute), 1971 June 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1178)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Huntley and J. Kilpatrick
- Mary (Coto) Sells, 1971 July 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1179)
  2 layers on the tape sounds like a long delayed echo.
  Interviewed and recorded by C. G. Crampton, V. Anderson, and E. Watson
- Code Talkers Reunion (Evening Session), 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1180)
  Navajo Code Talkers Reunion
- Sounds of Reunion, 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1181)
  "Beer Alley"
  Interviewed and recorded by C. G. Crampton
- Fred Cleveland, 1971 July 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1182)
  Assistant Curator at the Navajo Tribal Museum in Window Rock, Arizona.
- Linda Aranajo, Linda Blue, Juliann Romon, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1183)
  Interviewed and recorded by M. J. DeCarlo
- Reverend Emmett Soraano, 1971 June 01; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1184)
  Interviewed and recorded by Marion Ryan
- Glen Wapp, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1185)
  Reel-to-reel audiotape,compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 20 minutes.
- Jane Leivas, 1971 April 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1186)
  Life in a small town as compared to life at the University of California, Los Angeles.
  Interviewed and recorded by Priscilla Shames
- Gloria Esqueira, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1187)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 3 minutes.
- Margaret H. Cambel (Hopi), 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1188)
  Naming process, personal background and family background, religion, occupation, adolescent Native Americans, Hopi traditions and beliefs.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 29 minutes.
- Louis Scott, 1971 June 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1189)
- Lee Coppick, 1971 April 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1190)
- Frank Boudinot (Cherokee), 1971 June 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1191)
  Personal background, family background, education, military services, family involvment in Cherokee newspaper, personal career, Cherokee ledgends, family clan names and the ledgend of adopting surnames.
  Interviewed and recorded by Helen Amgwerd in Longbeach, Ca.
- Randy Edmunds, 1971 June 04; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1192)
  Unknown- Sounds like a conference of some sort.
  Interviewed and recorded by Marion Ryan in Hollywood, California
- Judson Bradley, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1193)
- Judson Bradley, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1194)
  Native American Urbanization Project. Discrimination.
- Lebain Johns, 1971 July 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1195)
  Interviewed and recorded by Sharon Galassi in Casa Grande, Arizona
- Ross V. Saboleff (Thinglit), 1971 June 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1196)
  College and life in Los Angeles
  Interviewed and recorded by Priscilla Shames in Los Angeles, California
- Stanley Lyman, 1968 June 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1197)
  "Running an Indian Reservation" Lecture
  Utah and the West Workshop
- June Lyman, 1965 June 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1198)
  "Problems in Educating the American Indian"
  Recorded by G. C. Thompson
- Robert Bennett, 1968 June 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1199)
- Sam Martinez, 1971 August 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1200-1A)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Viers and J. D. Sylvester. Translated by B. Lee.
- Sam Martinez, 1971 August 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1200-1B)
  Original interview. Side 1 and side 2 are the same.
- Sam Martinez, 1971 August 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1200-2A)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 25 minutes.
- Sam Martinez, 1971 August 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1200-2B)
  Continuation of translation of interview.
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 10 minutes.
- Juan Martinez, 1971 August 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1201-I)
  Chapter House.
- Juan Martinez, 1971 August 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1201-II)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 20 minutes.
- Yanibah Pino, 1971 August 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1202-I)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 34 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester and M. Henio. Translation by B. Lee.
- Yanibah Pino, 1971 August 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1202-I)
- Chavez Coho, 1971 August 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1203-I)
  Translataion of original interview.
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 43 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester, J. Viers, and M. Henio. Translated by B. Lee.
- Chavez Coho, 1971 August 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1203-I)
- George Raphaelito, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1204-I)
- George Raphaelito, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1204-II)
- Bi-gee-bah Pino Martin, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1205-I)
- Bi-gee-bah Pino Martin, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1205-II)
- K. Chee Martine, 1971 August 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1206-I&II)
  Translation of original tape.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 12 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester and J. Viers. Translated by B. Lee.
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1207)
- Rose Keith, 1971 August 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1208-I&II)
  Personal history, weaving, arts and crafts.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 7 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Scheib and E. Scheib
- Virginia Smith, 1971 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1209-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 41 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Scheib
- Rachael Eyetoo, 1971 July 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1210-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 54 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Shumway and G. Scheib
- Benton Keith, 1971 July 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1211-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 16 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Scheib
- John Guy, 1971 July 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1212)
- Clay Lockett, 1971 August 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1213-I,II,III)
  3 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 30 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Scheib for the Museum of Northern Arizona.
- Jim Hunt, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1214)
- Sherman Hatch, 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1215-I)
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Scheib and E. Schieb
- Sherman Hatch, 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1215-II)
- John Hanson, 1971 August 11; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1216)
  Recording of a lecture.
- Robert Hosler, 1971 August 11; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1217)
- H. Baxter Liebler, 1971 July 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1218)
- Father Wayne Pontious, 1971 July 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1219)
- Manson Jones, 1971 August 31; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1220-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 30 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow and N. Bulow
- Robert Young, 1971 August 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1221)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 2 minutes.
- Wilson Skeet, 1971 August 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1222-I&II)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 33 minutes.
- Paul Blatchford- Navajo Code Talker, 1971 August 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1223-I&II)
  Code Talking
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (2 CD) Total running time 2 hours 7 minutes.
- Hola Tsu (Navajo), 1971 September 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1224-I)
  Life story, history of N.A.C
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow and M. Metteba
- Hola Tsu (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1224-I)
- Father Silver, 1971 July 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1225)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 36 minutes.
- John Ake (Navajo), 1971 August 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1226-I&II)
  Cross Canyon
  Tracks 1-6 are the translation, and tracks 7-10 are the original interview.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 46 minutes.
- Benjabah Blackgoat (Navajo), 1971 August 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1227-I&II)
  Coal Mine
  Tracks 1-6 are the translation, and tracks 7-11 are the original interview.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 54 minutes.
- Peter Sandoval-Code Talker, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1228)
  Chinle
- Paul Merrill, 1971 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1229)
  Ft. Wingate
- Tony Tsosie (Navajo), 1971 July 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1230-I)
  Coal Mine.
- Tony Tsosie (Navajo), 1971 July 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1230-II)
  Continuation of original interview. (tape II follows tape III)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 50 min,
- Tony Tsosie (Navajo), 1971 July 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1230-III)
- Link Officer; James Officer-Pecos Conference, 1971 August; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1231-I&II)
  Problems in archaeology and anthropology field work in Native American areas; Pecos Conference-Discussion of Antiquities Law.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 37 minutes.
- Scott Preston, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1232-I)
  Ganado
- Scott Preston, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1232-II)
- Scott Preston, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1232-III)
- Scott Preston, 1971 July 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1232-IV)
- Diwizhi Begay (Navajo), 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1233-I)
  Lower Greasewood-Stories of Utes, Hopis, Mexicans, Wolf Men, and Anglos.
- Diwizhi Begay (Navajo), 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1233-II)
  First tape of original interview in native language.
- John Begay (Navajo), 1971 August 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1234-I)
  Coyote Canyon-Stories about Utes and other Native Americans: Old Game, Life Stories, and Jokes.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 1 minute.
- John Begay (Navajo), 1971 August 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1234-II)
- John Begay (Navajo), 1971 August 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1234-III)
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-I)
  Coyote Canyon-Place names, Anasazi, and Shoe Game.
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-II)
  Continuation of translation of original interview.
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-III)
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-IV)
  Second tape of original interview in native language.
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-V)
  Thrid tape of original interview in native language.
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-VI)
  Fourth tape of original interview in native language.
- Frank Becenti (Navajo), 1971 July 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1235-VII)
  Fifth tape of original interview in native language.
- Bernadine Whitegoat (Navajo), 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1236-I)
  Life story, Land Claims, Ute-Navajo Wars, Hopi, and Sacred Mountains.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 2 hr.
- Bernadine Whitegoat (Navajo), 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1236-II)
- Bernadine Whitegoat (Navajo), 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1236-III)
- Bernadine Whitegoat (Navajo), 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1236-IV)
- Bernadine Whitegoat (Navajo), 1971 July 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1236-V)
  Third tape of original interview in native language.
- Paul Brady (Apachi), 1971 July 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1237-I)
  Black House-Round Rock and Bizhoshi-Beautiful Mountain.
- Paul Brady (Apachi), 1971 July 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1237-II)
  Original Interview in native language.
- Peter Gishey (Navajo), 1971 August 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1238)
- Talley Chee (Navajo), 1971 July 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1239)
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow. Translated by B. Lee
- Nakai Snez (Navajo), 1971 August 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1240)
  Life story, stories about Ft. Wingate, farming near St. Michaels, hauling freight, use of sweat house.
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow and M. Metteba. Translated by B. Lee
- BIA New Teacher Orientation, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1241)
  Navajo Religion, Head Start Program.
  Recorded by N. Bulow.
- Red Wiskers; Joe Woody, 1971 August 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1242)
  Life story, fights with Bizhoshi, killing of Cross Canyon Traders.
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow. translated by B. Lee.
- Mrs. Kennedy, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1243)
  Mrs. Kennedy, author of two books on early life in New Mexico and Arizona, discusses life as the wife of an early trader.
- Sam Chischilly (Navajo), 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1244)
  Ft. Defiance
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow, translated by B. Lee
- Hosteen Se, 1971 July 18; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1245)
- Tom Ration, 1971 August 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1246)
  Smith Lake
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil and G. C. Thompson. Translated by B. Lee.
  Running Time: 20 minutes.